※ Using SQL with Python is a great idea for building complicated business logics 
   and also to have a single interface to run queries and perform analysis.
※ It is important to understand the business objectives and context
   prior to starting any type of analysis.
※ Concerning churn, the most important variables related to it includes 
   contract, monthly charges, and some services (internet, phone, and multiple lines).
※ People who stay with a company longer normally lead to higher LTVs,
   and enforcing 2- or 1-year contracts can help with this.
※ We can and must categorize people as having high and low LTVs.